<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<i18n baseKey="m.website.document.page" lcid="en_GB">
  <key id="document-name">page</key>
  <key id="edition-form-title">page properties</key>
  <key id="generalities">main properties</key>
  <key id="publication">publication</key>
  <key id="referencing">page meta-information</key>
  <key id="principalinformations">main properties</key>
  <key id="titleinformations">page title</key>
  <key id="layoutinformations">page layout</key>
  <key id="dateinformations">publication date</key>
  <key id="label">page name</key>
  <key id="label-help">document title strictly for internal use, used for displaying the document in the Backoffice.</key>
  <key id="navigationtitle">link text</key>
  <key id="navigationtitle-help">short title for navigation elements (menus, breadcrumb, etc. - 80 characters max.)</key>
  <key id="metatitle">page title</key>
  <key id="metatitle-help">
Full title displayed in your browser's title bar (corresponds to the TITLE tag used for referencing).
Recommended size: 60 to 80 characters. Put the most important keywords first.
This title will be completed by the website name if the option
			″Append website's name to the title of the pages″
is enabled on the website.</key>
  <key id="template">page template</key>
  <key id="template-help">If the original template has been modified, update it by pressing the opposite button.</key>
  <key id="updatetemplate">update the template</key>
  <key id="updatetemplatequestion">Do you really want to update this page template? A bad template can corrupt the existing content…</key>
  <key id="skin">skin</key>
  <key id="skin-help">drop a skin here to apply it to the element</key>
  <key id="description">description</key>
  <key id="description-help">description of the page for the search engines. Recommended size: between 160 and 180 characters. Place the most important keywords first.</key>
  <key id="startpublicationdate">start</key>
  <key id="startpublicationdate-help">The start publication date indicates the first date on which visitors will be able to view the page. Before this date, it will be impossible to view the page.</key>
  <key id="endpublicationdate">end</key>
  <key id="endpublicationdate-help">The end publication date indicates the latest date on which visitors will be able to view the page. After this date, it will be impossible to view the page.</key>
  <key id="indexinginformations">search</key>
  <key id="indexingstatus">indexable page</key>
  <key id="indexingstatus-help">enable/disable page indexing</key>
  <key id="keywords">keywords</key>
  <key id="keywords-help">Comma-separated keywords related to the page. Limit to keywords that most match the page contents.</key>
  <key id="author">author</key>
  <key id="author-help">name of the page author</key>
  <key id="navigationvisibility">visibility</key>
  <key id="navigationvisibility-help">visibility in navigation menus</key>
  <key id="ishomepage">website homepage</key>
  <key id="isindexpage">parent topic's index page</key>
  <key id="default-version-label">version No.{count} of {label}</key>
  <key id="usehttps">Secure mode (HTTPS)</key>
  <key id="usehttps-help">It will only be possible to access the page with a URL starting with ″https://″. With this option, the server must be configured to accept HTTPS connections</key>
  <key id="robotsmeta">Robot management</key>
  <key id="isindexpageforsubtopics">Index for the sub-topics</key>
  <key id="isindexpageforsubtopics-help">Index for the sub-topics, only when the page is functionally tagged</key>
</i18n>
